(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T23:06:52.263364",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ホロレンジャー 生誕3Dヒーローショー
[Title: HoloRanger Birthday 3D Hero Show]
迫るショッカー 地獄の軍団
Approaching Shocker, the legion of hell
我らを狙う 黒い影
Black shadows targeting us
世界の平和を守るため
To protect the peace of the world
ゴーゴー・レッツゴー 輝くマシン
Go! Go! Let's Go! Shining machine
ライダー (ジャンプ！)
Rider (Jump!)
ライダー (キック！)
Rider (Kick!)
仮面ライダー 仮面ライダー
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
ライダー ライダー
Rider, Rider
ライダー (ジャンプ！)
Rider (Jump!)
ライダー (キック！)
Rider (Kick!)
仮面ライダー 仮面ライダー
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
ライダー ライダー
Rider, Rider
第1話 ヒーロー爆誕！？ 雪花ラミィの旅立ち！
Episode 1: Hero Explosive Birth!? Snowflower Lamy Sets Off!
あんつぅ...
Phew, so hot...
いや、火薬の量間違えて爆発させすぎちゃったよ...
I totally miscalculated the gunpowder and made it explode way too much...
もう、せっかくの眉毛が焦げちゃうよ〜
Geez, my precious eyebrows are gonna get singed~
あ！雪民さん！ありがとう〜！
Ah! Yukimin! Thank you~!
おっ！みんな〜！今日は来てくれてありがとう！
Oh! Everyone~! Thank you for coming today!
そうです！今日はラミィの誕生日です！
That's right! Today is Lamy's birthday!
そして、今年のラミィは一味違います！
And this year, Lamy is a little different!
今年も体力作りで力をつけてきたけど、みんな知ってる？なんでラミィがあんなに頑張ってたか？
I've been working out to build up strength this year too, but do you know why Lamy was working so hard?
実はね... ヒーローになるためなんだー！
Actually... it's to become a hero!
どどーん！
Ta-da!
でも、ヒーローと言っても色んな形があるじゃん？
But even saying "hero", there are all kinds of forms, right?
だから今日は、自分だけのヒーロー像を探す旅に出ようと思うの！
So today, I'm going to set out on a journey to find my own ideal hero!
な、何だ！？
W-What is this!?
や、やめろー！
S-Stop it!
おりゃー！
Take this!
ゆ、雪民さん！
Yu-Yukimin!
雪民さん！ラミィを守ってくれたのー！？
Yukimin! You protected Lamy!?
さっきもバイク片付けてくれたし！
You even cleared away my bike earlier too!
雪民さんは本当にえらいなぁ〜！よしよしよしよし...
Yukimin is really so great~! Good boy, good boy...
あ！だいふくもいたの？
Ah! Daifuku was here too?
ちょっとまた敵が来ないか見張っといて〜
Keep an eye out in case enemies come again~
今日はね、色んなゲストを呼んでたくさんのヒーローを見ることができるから、楽しみだね！
Today, we invited various guests so we can see lots of heroes, so I'm looking forward to it!
それじゃあ、雪花ラミィ！ヒーロー探しの旅に行ってきまーす！
Well then, Snowflower Lamy! Off I go on my journey to find a hero!
なんで...
Why...
なんでまた雪民ばかり...
Why is it always Yukimin...
僕だって... 僕だって...
Even I... Even I...
ガッチャマンの歌
[Song Title: Gatchaman's Song]
誰だ 誰だ 誰だ
Who's that? Who's that? Who's that?
空のかなたに踊る影
The shadow dancing high in the sky...
白い翼の
With white wings,
ガッチャマン
it's Gatchaman!
命をかけて 飛び出せば
When you risk your life and leap out,
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
it's the Science Ninja Technique: Firebird!
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman!
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman!
地球は一つ
There is only one Earth,
there is only one Earth!
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman! Gatchaman!
誰だ 誰だ 誰だ
Who's that? Who's that? Who's that?
海の地獄に潜む影
The shadow lurking in the hell of the sea...
強い勇気の
With mighty courage,
ガッチャマン
it's Gatchaman!
嵐をさいて 雲きれば
Rending the storm and parting the clouds,
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
it's the Science Ninja Technique: Firebird!
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman!
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman!
地球は一つ
There is only one Earth,
there is only one Earth!
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman! Gatchaman!
誰だ 誰だ 誰だ
Who's that? Who's that? Who's that?
ビルの谷間に忍ぶ影
The shadow hiding between the skyscrapers...
赤い血潮の
With hot red blood,
ガッチャマン
it's Gatchaman!
夕日を浴びて 駆け出せば
Basking in the sunset as he dashes forth,
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
it's the Science Ninja Technique: Firebird!
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman!
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman!
地球は一つ
There is only one Earth,
there is only one Earth!
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman! Gatchaman!
ハッ ハッ
Ha, ha!
Go! Go! Muscle!
リングに 稲妻走り
Lightning strikes across the ring,
炎の戦士を てらす
illuminating the warrior of flame!
飛び散れ キン肉ビーム
Scatter, Kinniku Beam!
勝利に向かって
Heading straight toward victory!
私は（ドジで） 強い（つもり） キン肉マン
I'm Kinnikuman, clumsy yet acting tough!
走る（すべる） 見事に（ころぶ）
Running, slipping, falling down spectacularly!
ああ 心に愛がなければ
Ah, if you don't have love in your heart,
スーパーヒーローじゃないのさ
you're no superhero!
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman, Go Fight!
ハッ ハッ
Ha, ha!
Go! Go! Muscle!
嵐の必殺技で
With a storm of finisher moves,
けちらす超人レスラー
scattering superhuman wrestlers!
マットに真っ赤な薔薇が
On the ring mat, crimson roses
今夜も咲くのさ
will bloom again tonight!
私は（ドジで） 強い（つもり） キン肉マン
I'm Kinnikuman, clumsy yet acting tough!
誰もが（誰も） 待って（いない）
Nobody, absolutely nobody is waiting for me!
ああ 果てない夢を追いかけ
Ah, chasing after an endless dream...
Ah, chasing endless dreams,
スーパーヒーローになるのさ
I'll become a superhero.
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman Go Fight!
私は (ドジで) 強い (つもり) キン肉マン
I'm (clumsy) strong (in my mind), Kinnikuman!
走る (すべる) 見事に (ころぶ)
Running, (slipping), gracefully (falling).
ああ 心に愛がなければ
Ah, if there is no love in your heart,
スーパーヒーローじゃないのさ
you're not a superhero.
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman Go Fight!
聞こえないように 俯く体を
So as not to hear, bowing my body down,
誰か包んで...壊れる前に
someone wrap me up... before I break.
弾き出し嘲笑い 瞳を打つ
Repelling, sneering, striking my eyes,
闇への引き金
a trigger to the darkness.
踏み込む強さより 抗う痛みなら
Rather than the strength to step forward, if it's the pain of resisting,
誰より慣れっこで 食らう Conscience
I'm more used to it than anyone, devouring Conscience.
引き千切られたプライドが 心に巻くフリザード
Torn-apart pride, a blizzard wrapping around the heart.
ねえ ここから出してよって 叫んでいいの？
"Hey, take me out of here," is it okay to scream that?
埋もれた声は低い空が いつも救ってくれたね
My buried voice, the low sky always saved me, didn't it?
砕かれた幻想の果て でもまだ終わらせない
At the end of shattered illusions, but I won't let it end yet.
My heart will doubt...
悲しみ宿った 花びらに伝う
Dwelling in sorrow, trickling down the petals,
涙が落ちた 儚き結晶
tears fell, a fleeting crystal.
未来さえ試されて 篩にかけて 残った現実
Even the future is tested and sifted, leaving behind reality.
寡黙に見つめ合う 夕陽はこの鼓動 生かしてくれるだろう
Silently staring at each other, the sunset will keep this heartbeat alive.
惑う With the truth
Bewildered, with the truth.
転んだ今日がまとわりつく 萎れた感情伏せて
The fallen today clings to me, hiding withered emotions.
ねえ 早く気づいてよって 叫んでいいの？
"Hey, notice me quickly," is it okay to scream that?
傾いた視界に宿る 道は見分けられるか
Dwelling in the tilted vision, can the path be distinguished?
ゲームは始まったばかり この世に潜む現在(いま)を
The game has just begun, confronting the present lurking in this world.
My heart will want...
いらない痛みなんてないんだと 素直な自分足して
Saying there's no such thing as useless pain, adding my honest self,
ねえ ここまで来たよって 褒めてもいいの？
"Hey, I made it this far," is it okay to praise me?
埋もれた声は低い空が いつも救ってくれたね
My buried voice, the low sky always saved me, didn't it?
砕かれた幻想の果て でもまだ終わらせない
At the end of shattered illusions, but I won't let it end yet.
My heart will believe
GO FIGHT! マジ マジ マジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi Magi Magiranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ! 勇気をこの手に
OK! All right! Courage in these hands
旅立て!
Set off on a journey!
君が超えたいものは何?
What is it that you want to overcome?
大空 逆風 昨日の自分
The open sky, headwind, yesterday's self
立ち向かう時 揺れ動く
When standing up to face it, trembling
その胸に湧き出すパワー
The power welling up in that chest
グリーングランド ピンクストーム
Green Grand, Pink Storm
ブルースプラッシュ イエローサンダー
Blue Splash, Yellow Thunder
レッドファイヤー
Red Fire
冒険の始まりさ
It's the start of an adventure
GO FIGHT! マジ マジ マジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi Magi Magiranger
限界チャレンジャー
A limit challenger
勇気という名の魔法を持ってる
Possessing the magic called courage
GO FIGHT! マジ マジ マジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi Magi Magiranger
夢見てフューチャー
Dreaming of the future
OK! オーライ! 明日をこの手に
OK! All right! Tomorrow in these hands
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Magiranger
旅立て!
Set off on a journey!
君が守りたいものは何?
What is it that you want to protect?
友情 プライド 見えない絆
Friendship, pride, invisible bonds
挫けそうな時 そばにいる
When on the verge of giving up, being by your side
笑顔に初めて気がつく
Noticing that smile for the first time
タウロス フェアリー
Taurus, Fairy
マーメイド ガルーダ
Mermaid, Garuda
フェニックス
Phoenix
5つの手 重ねたら
When five hands overlap
GO FIGHT! マジ マジ マジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi Magi Magiranger
限界チャレンジャー
A limit challenger
勇気が勝利の道を示すから
Because courage shows the path to victory
GO FIGHT! マジ マジ マジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi Magi Magiranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ! この声よ届け
OK! All right! May this voice reach
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Magiranger
旅立て!
Set off on a journey!
唸る大地 風は吹き抜け
The roaring earth, the wind blowing through
たゆたう水 走る雷 燃える炎
Swaying water, running thunder, burning flame
GO FIGHT! マジ マジ マジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi Magi Magiranger
限界チャレンジャー
A limit challenger
勇気という名の魔法を持ってる
Possessing the magic called courage
GO FIGHT! マジ マジ マジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi Magi Magiranger
夢見てフューチャー
Dreaming of the future
OK! オーライ! 明日をこの手に
OK! All right! Tomorrow in these hands
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Magiranger
GO FIGHT! マジ マジ マジレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Magi Magi Magiranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ! 勇気をこの手に
OK! All right! Courage in these hands
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Magiranger
旅立て!
Set off on a journey!
第2話 仲間の力！ 心が導くヒーローのカタチ！
Episode 2: The Power of Companions! The Shape of a Hero Guided by the Heart!
うーん... たくさんのヒーローと出会えて力はついたけど、なんだかいまいちピンと来ないんだよなぁ...
Hmm... I've met a lot of heroes and gained strength, but somehow it still doesn't quite click...
ラミィ
Lamy!
悩んでる顔してどうしたの？
You look troubled, what's wrong?
あ、かなた！
Ah, Kanata!
そうなの… ヒーローってどうあるべきかわかんなくなっちゃって…
That's it... I don't really know how a hero should be anymore...
力があるだけじゃダメなんだ。
Having power alone isn't enough.
大事なのはその力をどう使うかだよ。
What matters is how you use that power.
かなた…
Kanata...
握力だけじゃ世界は変えられない。
Grip strength alone can't change the world.
人々の心を守るのも、ヒーローの大事な大事な仕事なんだから。
Protecting people's hearts is also a very, very important job for a hero.
そっか… 力で守れないものもあるよね。
I see... There are things you can't protect with power alone, right?
そう！だからヒーローにも強い心が必要なんだ！
Right! That's why heroes need a strong heart too!
どんなにピンチになっても、乗り越えるためにどんどん強くなる心が！
No matter how tight a spot you're in, a heart that keeps getting stronger to overcome it!
さあ、僕と一緒に歌って強い心を掴み取ろう！
Now, sing with me and grab hold of a strong heart!
うん！
Yeah!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
プリティでキュキュア 2人は プリキュア〜！
Pretty with Cure-Cure, the two of us are Pretty Cure~!
一難去って また一難 ぶっちゃけありえない！！
One problem after another, totally unbelievable!!
制服着てても ふたりは むちゃくちゃタフだし
Even in school uniforms, the two of us are super tough
お互いピンチを乗り越えるたび
Every time we overcome a pinch together
強く近く（強く近く）なるね☆
We become stronger and closer (stronger and closer)☆
Yeah!
your best! my best! 生きてるんだから 失敗なんて メッじゃない！
your best! my best! We're alive, so failing is no big deal at all!
笑う門に福来るでしょ！ ネガティブだって ブッ飛ぶぅ〜！
Fortune comes to those who smile! Even negativity flies away~!
生命（いのち）の花 咲かせて！ 思いっきり〜 もっとバリバリ！！
Let the flower of life bloom! With all our might~ Even more intensely!!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
プリティでキュキュア 2人は プリキュア〜！
Pretty with Cure-Cure, the two of us are Pretty Cure~!
たまには放課後のほほんと おしゃべり Very time!
Sometimes enjoying relaxed chat after school Very time!
ウワサは恋する乙女の ビタミン剤だもん
Rumors are a vitamin supplement for girls in love, after all
闇夜に浮かんだ虹のかけ橋
A rainbow bridge floating in the dark night
ここに降りて（ここに降りて）奇跡☆
Descend down here (descend down here) Miracle☆
Yeah!
your best! my best! 全力だから 友情、愛情、サイコー！
your best! my best! Because we give it our all, friendship, love, the absolute best!
論より証拠の輝くえくぼ 必殺技で ハートキュン！
Proof over words, a shining dimple, Heart-Kyun with a special move!
瞳に、☆（ほし）映して！ 思いっきり〜 もっとキラキラ！！
Reflect stars in your eyes! With all our might~ Even more sparkling!!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
プリティでキュキュア 2人は プリキュア〜！
Pretty with Cure-Cure, the two of us are Pretty Cure~!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
（プリキュア Chu Chu プリキュア Sha ba da ba da）
(Pretty Cure Chu Chu Pretty Cure Sha ba da ba da)
（Chu Chu Ah Chu Chu Ah）
(Chu Chu Ah Chu Chu Ah)
明日は明日の風吹く マジ意味わかんない
Tomorrow brings tomorrow's wind, seriously makes no sense
今しか出来ない宿題 ガンばらなくっちゃ！
Homework that can only be done now, gotta do our best!
真逆のキャラでも あい通じてる
Even with opposite personalities, we understand each other
夢を生きる（夢を生きる）チカラ☆
The power to live our dreams (live our dreams)☆
Yeah!
your best! my best! 生きてるんだから 失敗なんて メッじゃない！
your best! my best! We're alive, so failing is no big deal at all!
笑う門に福来るでしょ！ ネガティブだって ブッ飛ぶぅ〜！
Fortune comes to those who smile! Even negativity flies away~!
生命（いのち）の花 咲かせて！ 思いっきり〜 もっとバリバリ！！
Let the flower of life bloom! With all our might~ Even more intensely!!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure
プリティでキュキュア 2人は プリキュア〜！
Pretty with Cure-Cure, the two of us are Pretty Cure~!
プリキュア プリキュア（Chu wa）
Pretty Cure, Pretty Cure (Chu wa)
ありがとう、かなた！ なんとなくヒーローって何かをつかめた気がするよ。
Thank you, Kanata! I feel like I've somewhat grasped what a hero is.
よかった！ きっとラミィなら素敵なヒーローになれるよ。
I'm glad! I'm sure you can become a wonderful hero, Lamy.
その人を思いやる気持ちを忘れずにね。
Don't forget that feeling of caring for others, okay?
分かった！ ラミィなりのヒーロー像、考えてみるよ。 ありがとう！
Got it! I'll think about my own ideal hero image. Thank you!
それじゃあ… さらば〜！
Well then... Farewell~!
あー… いっちゃった。
Ah... She's gone.
よーし、この調子で次に行くぞー！
Alright, let me keep this momentum and move to the next!
あ
Ah...
ごめんね、だいふく
Sorry, Daifuku,
今忙しいの
I'm busy right now.
後でかまってあげるから
I'll play with you later, okay?
なんで...
Why...?
なんで僕だけ見てくれないんだ...
Why won't you look at only me...?
タラッタタラッタ タラッタタラッタ
Taratta taratta, taratta taratta
時に僕らは理想を語る非凡な才能の歌人で
At times, we are talented singers who speak of ideals,
またはキャピタリズムに屈する傀儡の卑しい子犬で
or vile puppies of puppets submitting to capitalism,
または主張が書かれたボードを掲げるデモの一員で
or members of a protest holding signs with our claims.
言わばあなたにとっての病ましい法螺吹き野郎の狼少年だ
In short, to you we are deceitful wolf boys, blowing hot air.
名声を 体裁を 人生そのものを 潰し合おう
Let's crush fame, appearances, and life itself.
恨んで 恨んで 恨んでもまた悔やんで
Hold a grudge, grudge, grudge, and regret it again,
拝みたい存在に背中を刺される
stabbed in the back by the one you wished to revere.
燃やして 燃やして 燃やしても手が震えて
Burn it, burn it, burn it, yet my hands tremble,
嘘を白昼堂々重ねて着込んだ
piling on and wearing lies in broad daylight.
分かって 分かって 分かって僕の正義を
Understand, understand, understand my justice,
無能な怪物を肥料で肥やした
fattening incompetent monsters with fertilizer.
妬んで 妬んで 妬んでいるまま選んだ
Envy, envy, chosen while still envying,
その程度のちゃちな正解はいらない
I don't need a cheap correct answer of that degree.
タラッタタラッタ タラッタタラッタ
Taratta taratta, taratta taratta
時に僕らは希望を託す聖人じみた歌人で
At times, we are saintly singers entrusting hope,
またはマキャバリズムを隠した見かけだけの置物で
or mere ornaments hiding Machiavellianism,
または全てに噛みつく振りだけ得意なエキストラで
or extras good at pretending to bite at everything.
やはりあなたにとっての病ましい法螺吹き野郎の狼少年だろう
Surely to you we are deceitful wolf boys, blowing hot air.
現状の 展望も 変貌も 何もかもが無価値なんだ
Current status, outlook, transformation—everything is worthless.
存在を 本能を 人生そのものを 消し合おう
Let me erase existence, instincts, and life itself.
恨んで 恨んで 恨んでもまた悔やんで
Hold a grudge, grudge, grudge, and regret it again,
拝みたい存在に背中を刺される
stabbed in the back by the one you wished to revere.
燃やして 燃やして 燃やしても手が震えて
Burn it, burn it, burn it, yet my hands tremble,
嘘を白昼堂々重ねて着込んだ
piling on and wearing lies in broad daylight.
分かって 分かって 分かって僕の正義を
Understand, understand, understand my justice,
無能な怪物を肥料で肥やした
fattening incompetent monsters with fertilizer.
妬んで 妬んで 妬んでいるまま選んだ
Envy, envy, chosen while still envying,
その程度のちゃちな正解はいらない
I don't need a cheap correct answer of that degree.
タラッタタラッタ タラッタタラッタ
Taratta taratta, taratta taratta
時に僕らは思想を諭す英雄的な歌人で
At times, we are heroic singers teaching ideology,
つまりあなたにとってのカリスマ気取った極悪非道なペテン師だ
in short, to you we are atrocious swindlers posing as charismatic.
ねぇ、生まれてから今日までの間 どれくらいのごはんで
Hey, how much food have we eaten from when we were born until today?
わたし達はできてるのかな 毎日ありがとう
Are we made of all that? Thank you every day.
もし食卓から おいしいが消えてしまったら ああ、迷わずに
If "delicious" disappeared from our dining table, ah, without hesitation,
どこにいたって 何をしてたって 取り戻しにいこう
no matter where we are or what we're doing, let's go get it back.
あれは記念日の記憶
That's a memory from an anniversary,
何気ないあの味も
even that ordinary taste,
忘れたりしない
I won't ever forget.
ずっと一緒だよって 伝えなくっちゃ
I have to tell you that we'll be together forever.
かならず！
For sure!
守りたいこの味は キミと笑いあう毎日の
This taste I want to protect is from every day laughing with you,
いちばん傍で照らす あたたかい道しるべなんだ
a warm beacon illuminating right by your side.
みんなと 今胸を熱くするオモイ 育んでこれからも
Cultivating these feelings with everyone that heat up our chests, from now on too,
大切に刻もう キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
let's cherish and etch them, a specialty bound by bonds.
ホラ、キミに届くおいしいの中の たくさんのストーリー
Look, inside the deliciousness delivered to you, there are so many stories.
めぐりめぐって ここにあるって 奇跡みたいだよ
Going round and round, the fact that it's right here feels like a miracle.
約束！ 繋げたい今がある キミと分け合いたい未来へと
I promise! There's a present I want to connect to a future I want to share with you.
くじけそうな時も 負けないココロで立ち向かう
Even when I feel like giving up, I'll face it with an unyielding heart.
みんなの しあわせなエナジーが作る この日々がうれしいよ
I'm so happy for these days created by everyone's happy energy.
デリシャスにあつまれ！ パーティは続いていくね
Gather deliciously! The party will keep on going.
世界中で今も
Even right now around the world,
それぞれのストーリー
each of our stories
ひとりずつが できることを
everyone is doing what they can
がんばってるから
and giving it their all.
かならず！ 守りたいこの味は キミと笑いあう毎日の
Without fail! The flavor I want to protect is from our days of laughing together,
いちばん傍で照らす あたたかい道しるべなんだ
a warm signpost shining right by our side.
みんなと 今胸を熱くする思い 育んでこれからも
Nurturing these feelings that warm our hearts with everyone from now on,
大切に刻もう キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
let me treasure and engrave this speciality bound by our bonds.
約束！ 繋げたい今がある キミと分け合いたい未来へと
I promise! There's a present I want to connect to a future I want to share with you.
くじけそうな時も 負けないココロで立ち向かう
Even when I feel like giving up, I'll face it with an unyielding heart.
みんなの しあわせなエナジーが作る この日々がうれしいよ
I'm so happy for these days created by everyone's happy energy.
デリシャスにあつまれ！ パーティは続いていくね
Gather deliciously! The party will keep on going.
大切に刻もう キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
Let's treasure and engrave this speciality bound by our bonds.
第3話 闇を超えて！ねぽらぼ絆ビームで奇跡を起こせ！
[Episode 3: Overcome the darkness! Cause a miracle with the NePoLaBo Bond Beam!]
やっぱりねぽらぼだね！
Nepolabo really is the best!
ねぽらぼ！ねぽらぼ！
Nepolabo! Nepolabo!
大福！やっと来てくれたー！
Daifuku! You finally came!
許さない... 許さない...！
Unforgivable... Unforgivable!
だ... 大福？！
D-Daifuku?!
まさか、あれは...！
No way, could that be...?
ラミィに構ってもらえず、負の感情が爆発して...
He couldn't get Lamy's attention, so his negative emotions exploded...
闇落ちした... やみふく...！
He fell to darkness... Yamifuku...!
そんな... 大福！元に戻って！
No way... Daifuku! Change back to normal!
うるさい！
Shut up!
こうなったら... 力尽くで元に戻してあげる！
If that's how it is... I'll force you back to normal by power!
元に戻って！
Turn back to normal!
うわぁぁぁ！
Uwaaa!
うわ！熱っ！
Whoa! Hot!
やりすぎじゃない？これ。
Didn't you go a bit too far with that?
すげー... 大丈夫？
Amazing... Are you okay?
ど、どうだ？！
H-How's that?!
くっそー！
Damn it!
大福！
Daifuku!
あ、ラミィ、待って！
Ah, Lamy, wait!
しつこーい！
You're so persistent!
ラミィー！
Lamy!
構ってー！
Pay attention to me!
うわー！ラミィちゃんが闇落ちさせられたー！
Whoa! Lamy-chan was corrupted to the dark side!
これでラミィはずーっと一緒だー！
Now Lamy will be together with you forever!
ラミィが相手でも止めるしかないよ！
Even if it's Lamy, we have no choice but to stop her!
確かに！ラミィはタフだしね！ま、多少痛くても平気でしょ！
True! Lamy is tough after all! Well, a little pain won't hurt, right?
あ、ちょうどいいところに！いくよゆきみ、手貸して！
Ah, just in time! Come on Yukimin, lend us a hand!
ゆきみさん、いっけー！そりゃー！
Yukimi-san, go! There!
ゆきみー！ごめーん！
Yukimi! I'm sorry!
いっけー！
Go!
邪魔してー！
Get out of the way!
まだだー！
Not yet!
えー！今度はラミィ、でっかくなっちゃったんだけどー！
What?! Now Lamy has gotten super huge!
仕方ない、あれを使おう。
It can't be helped. Let's use that.
おれ？
Huh?
そっか。よし。
Oh, right. Okay.
みんな、力を貸して！ラミィのいいところをたくさん言って！
Everyone, lend us your strength! Say lots of good things about Lamy!
祝福の力でパワーを溜めて、攻撃だ！
Let's gather power with the blessing of love and attack!
よし、いい感じ！このまま観客席のみんなも、ラミィのいいところ、めっちゃ言ってって！
Alright, looking good! Everyone in the audience, keep telling us Lamy's good points!
で、うちらもよ！
And us too!
え、うちらも言うの？
Wait, we have to say them too?
ラミィのいいところ言ってこう！
Let's share Lamy's good points!
そしたら多分ラミィも元に戻るから！
Then Lamy will probably go back to normal!
確かに。いつもの感じね。
True. The usual drill.
ねねから！ねねから！
Starting with Nene! Starting with Nene!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがあるー！
I have something to tell Lamy-chan!
なーにー？
What is it?
ねねのくだらないLINE、秒で返事してくれて、ありがとー！
Thank you for replying in seconds to my silly LINE messages!
あら、いいじゃない。
Oh, isn't that nice?
下がってる、下がってる！
It's dropping, it's dropping!
じゃあ次！おまる行け！
Next! Go, Omaru!
ラミィに言いたいことがありまーす！
I have something to tell Lamy!
なーにー？
What is it?
いつも頼りないうちらのことまとめてくれたり、ツッコんでくれたりして、本当に感謝してるんだ！だからラミィ、元の姿に戻ってー！
You always round us unreliable folks up and play the straight man, I'm really grateful! So Lamy, please go back to normal!
どうだ！？
How's that?!
あ、下がった下がった！
Ah, it dropped! It dropped!
じゃあ次！ししろん行け！
Then next! Go, Shishiron!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがあるー！
I have something to tell Lamy-chan!
なーにー？
What is it?
いつもししろんが小ボケをいっぱいすると、全部にツッコんでくれて、ありがとー！
Thank you for always reacting to every single one of my silly jokes!
すごい！めっちゃ下がってる！
Awesome! It's dropping so much!
ありがとう...
Thank you...
ねね行け！２個目！２周目！
Go Nene! Second round! Second lap!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがあるー！
I have something to tell Lamy-chan!
なーにー？
What is it?
秒で返事してくれるけど、スタンプで秒で終わらせようとするの、やめてねー！
You reply in seconds, but stop trying to end the chat in seconds with a sticker!
あ、上がるはず...
Ah, it's supposed to rise...
おまる行け！おまる行け！
Go Omaru! Go Omaru!
ラミィに言いたいことがあるー！
I have something to tell Lamy!
なーにー？
What is it?
これをきっかけに、初期ラミィからやり直してみるのはどうでしょうかー！？
Taking this opportunity, how about starting over from early Lamy-chan?!
バカお前！やめろ！やめろよ！
You idiot! Stop it! Stop it!
ああー！上がってる！上がっちゃダメだって！
Ahh! It's going up! Don't let it go up!
バカ垂れ！決めろ、決めるぞ！
You fool! Let's finish this!
ラミィちゃんに言いたいことがあるー！
I have something to tell Lamy-chan!
なーにー？
What is it?
いつもねぽらぼを大切にしてくれて、ありがとー！
Thank you for always cherishing Nepolabo!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
え、どういうこと？やってくれるんじゃないの？
Eh, what do you mean? Isn't it going to do something?
えー！これはいったい...
EH?! What on earth is this...
でも、パワーが溜まったんじゃないか？
But didn't it store up energy?
ラミィ、元に戻ってくれー！
Lamy, return to normal!
行け！ねぽらぼ絆ビーム！
Go! Nepolabo Bond Beam!
元に戻れー！
Return to normal!
ラミィ！ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy!
ラミィは一体...
What happened to me...
元に戻った！
You're back to normal!
大福の力により闇落ちしてたんだよ！
You fell into darkness because of Daifuku's power!
いや、でも正直、普段のラミィと全然変わんなかったから...
Well, to be honest, you weren't any different from normal Lamy...
元に戻ってよかった...
I'm glad you're back to normal...
あ！おい！大福！
Ah! Hey! Daifuku!
大福... ちゃんと見てあげられなくて...
Daifuku... I'm sorry for not taking proper care of you...
他人を思いやる気持ちが大切って教わったばかりなのに、うまくできなくて、ごめんね。
I was just taught how important it is to care about others, yet I couldn't do it right... I'm sorry.
やっぱりラミィには、大福や雪民さんがいないとダメなの。
After all, Lamy can't make it without Daifuku and Yukimin.
大福、ずっとずっと一緒だよ！
Daifuku, we'll be together forever and ever!
完
[End]
はい、ということで、みんな、ラミィの生誕祭どうでしたかー？
All right, everyone, how was Lamy's Birthday Festival?
面白かった！感動した！ラミィ誕生日おめでとう！
It was fun! I was moved! Happy Birthday, Lamy!
ということでね、まだ終わりませんよ！
So, it's not over yet!
重大告知が2つあります！
I have two major announcements!
まずは、こちら！
First, here it is!
雪花ラミィ 誕生日記念2025 グッズ！
Yukihana Lamy Birthday Celebration 2025 Goods!
ということで、詳しく紹介していきたいと思います！
So, I'd like to introduce them in detail!
まずはこちら！
First up is this!
まずはこちら、アクリルスタンドー！
First up is this acrylic stand!
テーマはですね、フード付きタオルを身につけたラミィの元気な姿となっております！
The theme is Lamy looking energetic in a hooded towel!
みんな飾ってね！
Everyone, please display it!
続いてはこちら、どん！おそろいトレーナー！
Next up is this! Boom! Matching sweatshirt!
これ欲しかったやつ！かわいい！
I wanted this! So cute!
これはですね、サイバー衣装のトレーナーとおそろいのデザインとなっております！
This design matches the sweatshirt from the cyber outfit!
みんな、ラミィとおそろいにして着てね！
Everyone, wear it to match with Lamy!
続いてはこちら！ぬいぐるみキーホルダー ファンタジー私服衣装ver.
Next up is this! Plushie Keychain: Fantasy Casual Outfit Ver.!
ユニーリアのね、あの夏衣装を身にまとったラミィのぬいぐるみキーホルダーとなっております！
It's a plushie keychain of Lamy wearing her Uniliah summer outfit!
これを身につけて、色んなところラミィとお出かけしてください！
Please wear it and go out with Lamy to all kinds of places!
探して続いてはこちら！雪民フード付きタオルとなっております！
And next up is this! The Yukimin Hooded Towel!
これね、雪民さんの顔がフードになっているタオルね！
This towel has Yukimin's face as a hood!
今後ね、イベントとかあったときに身につけてアピールしてくれると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you wear it at future events to show your support!
そして！フルセット購入特典はこちら！雪花ラミィ 箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入り描き下ろしポストカードとなっております！
And the full set purchase bonus is this! A newly drawn postcard with Yukihana Lamy's foil-stamped sign & message!
かわいいでしょう？みんなこれやって！イエーイ！ありがとうございます！
Isn't it cute? Everyone, do this pose! Yay! Thank you so much!
ということで、以上、雪花ラミィ 誕生日記念2025グッズでした！
That concludes the Yukihana Lamy Birthday Celebration 2025 Goods reveal!
そして、告知2つ目！こちら！新曲となっております！
And now, the second announcement! This one right here! It's a new song!
この配信のあと21時からフルアニメーションMVが公開されます！
After this stream, at 21:00, a full-animation MV will be released!
そうなんです！初めてのフルアニメーションMVとなっております！
That's right! It's my first ever full-animation MV!
みんな見てね！
Everyone, make sure to watch it!
各種音楽サイトのリリースはこのあと0時から配信されますのでよろしくお願いします！
Releases on various music streaming platforms start at midnight tonight, so please check them out!
はい、ということで！みんな今日はたくさんたくさんありがとう！
All right then! Thank you all so, so much today!
ありがとうねー！バイバーイ！
Thank you! Bye-bye!
バイバーイ！ありがとう！こっちこっち！
Bye-bye! Thank you! Over here, over here!
ということで、最後に新曲聴いていってください！
So, please stay and listen to my new song at the end!
それでは聴いてください。「無敵☆本気だサバイバー！」
Now then, please listen to "Muteki☆Honki da Survivor!"
ギリギリの綱渡り
Walking a tightrope on the edge,
弱音はポケットの奥
Hiding my weakness deep in my pocket,
しまい込んだら ただ進むだけ
Once tucked away, I just keep moving forward.
こけたって即リスタート
Even if I stumble, an immediate restart!
そこからがスタートライン
That's where the starting line begins!
もう止まらないよ
I won't stop anymore!
迷いなんてもう No No
Doubts are a No No now!
不器用でも 前へ
Even if clumsy, push forward!
しょげてる暇はなし
No time to feel down,
ハイテンションでいこうじゃん！
let's go with high energy!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible, totally serious survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
Even from zero, as many times as it takes,
メンタル最強モードで　見ててね★
in ultimate mental mode, keep watching me!★
限界歓迎チャレンジャー！
A challenger who welcomes all limits!
そう不安なんてさ　笑い飛ばそう
Yeah, let's just laugh away all our anxieties!
最前線　君次第
On the frontlines, it's up to you!
さあ　行こう Ready Go　ついてきてよね☆
Come on, let's go, Ready Go, follow right behind me!☆
トラブルさえ　追い風
Even trouble is a tailwind,
ピンチも　ドキドキのスパイス　"Bring it on!"　胸を張れ
crisis is thrilling spice, "Bring it on!" Stand proud!
遠回りも Go Go
Even taking a detour, Go Go!
転んでも Try だ！
Even if you fall, give it a Try!
自分史上　一番へ
Towards the absolute best version of myself!
アクセル全開　ノンストップ！
Pedal to the metal, non-stop!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible, totally serious survivor!
ブレーキなんてお飾りでしょ？
Brakes are just for decoration, right?
ハート高鳴りモードで　感じて★
Feel it in heart-pounding mode!★
完全☆燃焼フィニッシャー！
Complete combustion finisher!
そう誰より強く　夢を叫ぼう
Yeah, let's shout our dreams louder than anyone!
最終章　君次第
In the final chapter, it's up to you!
さあ　行こう Ready Go　置いてかないからっ☆
Come on, let's go, Ready Go, I won't leave you behind!☆
最強☆最愛チームメイツ！
Strongest, most beloved teammates!
君の声が　パワーソース
Your voice is my power source!
輝いて　駆けてこう
Shining bright, let's run forward,
未来へ Fly high...
Fly high into the future...
超ハイテンションでいこうじゃん！
Let's go with super high energy!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible, totally serious survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
Even from zero, as many times as it takes,
メンタル最強モードで　見ててね★
in ultimate mental mode, keep watching me!★
限界歓迎チャレンジャー！
A challenger who welcomes all limits!
そう不安なんてさ　笑い飛ばそう
Yeah, let's just laugh away all our anxieties!
最前線　君次第
On the frontlines, it's up to you!
さあ　行こう Ready Go　もっともっと　ついてきてよね☆
Come on, let's go, Ready Go, keep up with me even more!☆
みんな、今日のライブどうだった？
Everyone, how was today's live stream?
ラミィ、ヒーローになれたかな？
Do you think Lamy managed to become a hero?
新曲も、今までのラミィにはない、かっこいい曲だったでしょ？
The new song was really cool and different for me, right?
みんなの感想、今日のハッシュタグをつけていっぱい聞かせてね！
Please tell me all your thoughts using today's hashtag!
そして！この配信のあと、21時から...
And! After this stream, starting at 21:00...
新曲「無敵☆本気だサバイバー！」のフルアニメーションMVが公開されます！
...the full animation MV for my new song "Invincible & Serious Survivor!" will be released!
ついにやってきました、フルアニメーション！
It's finally here: full animation!
今回のMVには、ラミィの大好きなものがたくさん詰まっています！
This MV is packed full of things that I love!
このライブのあと、直接MVに飛ぶようになっているので、みんなこのまま待っててね！
You'll be redirected straight to the MV after this live stream, so please wait right here!
さて！まだもう少し時間があるから、MVをチラ見せしちゃいます！
Now then! We still have a little time left, so I'll give you a sneak peek of the MV!
どうぞ！
Here you go!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
[Invincible & Serious Survivor!]
Invincible, totally serious survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
Even from zero, as many times as it takes,
メンタル最強モードで　見ててね★
in ultimate mental mode, keep watching me!★
限界歓迎チャレンジャー！
A challenger who welcomes all limits!
そう不安なんてさ　笑い飛ばそう
Yeah, let's just laugh away all our anxieties!
最前線　君次第
On the frontlines, it's up to you!
さあ　行こう Ready Go　ついてきてよね☆
Come on, let's go, Ready Go, follow right behind me!☆
このあと　ミュージックビデオ公開！
[Music video coming up next!]